# **Vinay Joshi**

Email: vinay01joshi@gmail.com

Phone: +91 82856 11645



2005 - 2007

## **Summary**

A qualified IT Professional rich experience in Analyzing, Designing, Development, and Implementation of business applications in Client Server technology and file server technology with an exposure to different platforms and software systems. Possess expertise & experience in Azure C#, Asp.net,Asp.Net MVC, SQL Server, SQLCE, Mysql, Windows Mobile 6.0 Application.

# So what makes me unique? # I write clean, dry, solid code that anyone can read using best practices. People I worked with know me as a hard worker. For example, a project I worked on was nearing the deadline, but for reasons outside of our control, we were at least one month behind. I was able to bring our team together, and we were able to finish the fully tested final application two days before it was due. This helped our relation team close a bigger deal with the client, which I am now working.

## **Experience**

<b>△</b> OPTUM°	Senior Software Engineering Optum (formerly Alere Wellbeing)	Jul 2018 - Present
SR_	Senior Associate Technology SapientRazorfish	Jan 2017 - Jul 2018
\$	Associate Technology L2 SapientNitro	Feb 2014 - Dec 2016
NextGen IN YEAR COMP	Senior Software Developer NextGen Invent Corporation	Oct 2011 - Feb 2014
NextGen Invest comp	Software Developer NextGen Invent Corporation	Oct 2011 - Feb 2014
	Corporate Trainer HPES	Jul 2011 - Sep 2011

#### **Education**

Dehradun Institute of Technology (U.T.U. Dehardun) 2008-2011	2008 - 2011
Master of Computer Applications (MCA), computers, 73	



P.G.Collage Rishikesh
BSC, Math , Physics ,Geology

Working as a Dot Net Technical Support (Trainer)

#### **Skills**

C# • Angular 2 • Node.js • ASP.NET MVC • ASP.NET Core • Microsoft Azure • Microsoft SQL Server • JavaScript • Azure DevOps • Docker

### **Honors & Awards**



Pause for Applause • CEO Of Next Gen Invent Corporation • Feb 2012

This award Given me for Developing Barcode reader for windows Mobile machine Intermac C50



Core Value Award • Sapient • Mar 2015